<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ranting about fantasies</title>
    <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ranting about fantasies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.nolife4life.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S09</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s09/</guid>
      <description>Treading the treacherous undercity Group quickly rushed through the damp and dirty tunnel. Their steps were echoed by the sound of water jet slamming in the cobblestones and leathery wings swinging above the entrance to the tunnel. They delved deeper into what seemed to be abandoned passageways. Broken pieces of ancient architecture, remnants of cobblestone roads, towered by newly built structures. Fragments of blue sky shined through here and there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Character Chronicles: Ylva</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/hidden/ylva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/hidden/ylva/</guid>
      <description>Backstory   credit Michael C. Hayes
  Decades ago Gulbrand, a vagabond blacksmith from eastern Rubblebelt, came across an unusual bundle in the natures cradle: two girls wrapped in red and blue silk. He took the girls to a shaman of the Burning Tree Clan and asked if they are willing to take them in. Shaman, a wise old woman, saw kindness in Gulbrands char-black eyes sitting behind a lush beard and the tenderness in his large muscular build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S08</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s08/</guid>
      <description>In the name of Science! &amp;ldquo;We should close the portal&amp;rdquo;, Katrille started after the dust of their last fight calmed down.
&amp;ldquo;Any ideas on how are we going to do that?&amp;rdquo;, Wataru looked at his own blood on his palms. &amp;ldquo;Maybe we can leave this to the local goblins?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I suggest we throw bricks into it until it is full!&amp;rdquo;, Shinigami proclaimed, her suggestion bouncing off two stone like faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elven Genocide</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/hidden/elf_genocide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/hidden/elf_genocide/</guid>
      <description>Painful love It was a bright summer day when I stepped out from my transport thopter to shores of Jezeru. I knew about this part of the world only by the handful of facts I got from local notary&amp;rsquo;s office. This area had been marked for reclamation fourteen hundred years ago and officially purchased by Simic few hundred years later. Naturally all paperwork was handled by Orzhov, major member of Ozbedat was involved in this transaction, did not really took the time to distinguish which of the dead farts was behind it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S07</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s07/</guid>
      <description>Wisest of choices Darkness had already consumed alleyways of Ravnica when the party exited Neirius lab. Large streets were fighting off the dark with magilight posts and lamps held by Azorius patrols. Motion in the streets had reduced a quite a bit when compared to the middle of the day, but Ravnica never truly sleeps. In this district people were minding their own business at this hour. Usually open corner stands were no longer there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S06</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s06/</guid>
      <description>Darkness awaits Rumbling came louder and louder, eventually manifesting as a cloud of dust and debris at the far side of the cavern.
&amp;ldquo;RUN!&amp;rdquo; Wataru trumpeted and did exactly that, with a heavy piece of machinery under his arm.
It did not require much more persuasion for others as a huge beetle emerged angry from the dust cloud. It was running directly at the party, it&amp;rsquo;s three humongous horns were reflecting light from luminescent spores and mushrooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S05</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s05/</guid>
      <description>Hand of the numbered The girls exited the damp and magilit Zonot back to the surface.
&amp;ldquo;I will leave you now. I feel that Wataru soul is bound to return to his body soon, and the song is calling me back to my duty in the forest.&amp;rdquo; Neia looked longingly at the clear skies, &amp;ldquo;Blessings of Mat&amp;rsquo;Selesnya to you all&amp;rdquo;.
The party looked after the elvish girl and her wolf striding into the alleys of The Blistercoils.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S04</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s04/</guid>
      <description>Way to life Grim atmosphere loomed in the small sparsely decorated room.
&amp;ldquo;So, what are we going to do with the dead elephant in the room?&amp;rdquo; Shinigami broke the silence, slowly poking thick loxodon&amp;rsquo;s skin with her flute.
&amp;ldquo;I know of a scientific way to bring our friend here back from the astral plane. It requires a tiny bit of science and a skilled biochemist.&amp;rdquo; Katrille started, &amp;ldquo;When I was learning in the Prism university, we had a course about revivification potions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S03</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s03/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps some necessary evil 10076 Mokosh 8
Group woke up in the darkened interior of a livewood hut. Through tightly shut window blinds noise seeped from outside. Voices of children were responding to silky smooth elven voice. From what the party gathered Wyn was teaching children to take care after injured animals.
Wataru, Nai and Katrille looked around their little shelter. It was not poor, but not fancy either. Everything seemed in place and cared after, sun beams were leaking into the interior making light strips in the pollen filled air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S02</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s02/</guid>
      <description>Having a polite groin grabbing Dark alleyway, where Wataru and Nai had stopped to inspect Neirius&amp;rsquo; condition previously empty and desolate filled with action and tension. Out of the blue vedalken turned a corner and bumped into firm loxodons back.
&amp;ldquo;Ach!&amp;rdquo; blueish creature exhaled.
&amp;ldquo;What just&amp;hellip;?&amp;rdquo; Wataru started a sentence as a ghostly skeletal hand appeared out of the thin mist and grabbed his smaller snout and clutched painfully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S01</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s01/</guid>
      <description>Unlikely acquaintances 10076 Mokosh 7
The evening crowd was thick. A heavily panting young boy was pushing through it looking for someone. His eyes blinked quickly while filtering the faces in the crowd. Suddenly his gaze fixed on a loxodon at the side of the street calmly browsing through some merchandise.
&amp;ldquo;Here you go sir&amp;rdquo;, the courier said under his breath and pressed a piece of paper into thick elephant hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 00:31:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a developer (of sorts) currently leading a DnD campaign set in Ravnica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun with flags</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/blog/fun-with-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/blog/fun-with-flags/</guid>
      <description>Every now and then I catch myself in such situation:
enum Alignment { Left, Center, Right, Justify, }; enum Anchor { Top, Right, Bottom, Left, }; void SetAnchor(byte anchor); void SetAlignment(byte alignment);  This just begs for errors. So what can we do here? Obvious answer &amp;ndash; lets make a class, with overloaded operator| and voilia, we just created a type safe flag implementation. This time I wanted to do something different, in a way, that performance of these flags would match (in some extent) natural binary operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Functions</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/blog/tackling-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 21:53:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/blog/tackling-functions/</guid>
      <description>Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve found this post, which describes a better implementation of std::functions. Since I had severe problems with understanding how this code works, I decided to write down my adventures in it step by step.
Syntax The code in question provides an alternate implementation of std::function, so at least it should make such code work:
int foo(int a) {}; func::function&amp;lt;int(int)&amp;gt; f(foo); f(5);  I started analyzing this code by searching for a definition of function.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>