<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Story on Ranting about fantasies</title>
    <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Story on Ranting about fantasies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.nolife4life.org/story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S05</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s05/</guid>
      <description>Hand of the numbered The girls exited the damp and magilit Zonot back to the surface.
&amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;I will leave you now. I feel that Wataru soul is bound to return to his body soon, and the song is calling me back to my duty in the forest.&amp;ldquo;- Neia looked longingly at the clear skies, -&amp;ldquo;Blessings of Mat&amp;rsquo;Selesnya to you all&amp;rdquo;.
The party looked after the elvish girl and her wolf striding into the alleys of Blistercoils.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S04</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s04/</guid>
      <description>Way to life Grim atmosphere loomed in the small sparsely decorated room.
&amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;So, what are we going to do with the dead elephant in the room?&amp;rdquo;- Shinigami broke the silence, slowly poking thick loxodon&amp;rsquo;s skin with her flute.
&amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;I know of a scientific way to bring our friend here back from the astral plane. It requires a tiny bit of science and a skilled biochemist.&amp;ldquo;- Katrille started, -&amp;ldquo;When I was learning in the Prism university, we had a course about revivification potions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S03</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s03/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps some necessary evil Group woke up in the darkened interior of a livewood hut. Through tightly shut window blinds noise seeped from outside. Voices of children were responding to silky smooth elven voice. From what the party gathered Wyn was teaching children to take care after injured animals.
Wataru, Nai and Katrille looked around their little shelter. It was not poor, but not fancy either. Everything seemed in place and cared after, sun beams were leaking into the interior making light strips in the pollen filled air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S02</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s02/</guid>
      <description>Having a polite groin grabbing Dark alleyway, where Wataru and Nai had stopped to inspect Neirius&amp;rsquo; condition previously empty and desolate filled with action and tension. Out of the blue vedalken turned a corner and bumped into firm loxodons back.
&amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;Ach!&amp;rdquo;- blueish creature exhaled.
&amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;What just&amp;hellip;?&amp;rdquo;- Wataru started a sentence as a ghostly skeletal hand appeared out of thin mist and grabbed his smaller snout and clutched painfully.
&amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;HRGMTH!&amp;rdquo;- surprised elephant released a weird and awkward sound into the alley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravnica S01</title>
      <link>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nolife4life.org/story/ravnica_s01/</guid>
      <description>Unlikely acquaintances Evening crowd was thick. A heavily panting young boy was pushing through looking for someone. His eyes blinked quickly while filtering the faces of the crowd. Suddenly his gaze fixated on a loxodon at the side of the street calmly browsing through some merchandise.
&amp;ndash; “Here you go sir”-, the courier said under his breath and pressed a piece of paper into thick elephant hand.
&amp;ndash; “Mhm”-, murmured the ‘phant, while nodding and with a motion of his large head hinted the boy that he should leave now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>